An apocalyptic Alice in Wonderland!
Black Moon is a fantasy, horror, mystery film directed by Louis Malle.
There is a global civil war between men and women.
A teenage girl tries to escape this reality and arrives at a hidden place where a strange unicorn lives with a family:
sister, brother, many children and an old, bedridden woman who stays in contact with the world through her radio.
Lily, played by Cathryn Harrison.
Old Lady (as Thérèse Giehse), played by Therese Giehse.
Sister Lily, played by Alexandra Stewart.
Brother Lily, played by Joe Dallesandro.
Black Moon is a 1975 Franco-German experimental fantasy horror film directed by Louis Malle and
starring Cathryn Harrison, Joe Dallesandro, Therese Giehse and Alexandra Stewart.
Though produced in France, its dialogue is in English.
It is dedicated to Giehse, who died shortly after shooting had completed.
The film opened in France on 24 September 1975 before screening at the 1975 New York Film
Festival, with North American distribution overseen by 20th Century Fox.
The film explores themes of dreams, sibling
relationship, brother, allegory, surreal.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.